foreign
[Music]
heart disease or diabetes easily
for my retirement
i want to invest in a plan
that takes care of my health care
expenses and also gives me regular
income
to take care of my daily expenses
presenting a retirement plan specially
designed for your needs
icici prove guaranteed pension plan
flexi this plan is designed for people
between the age of 45 to 60 years and
looking to save for their retirement
the plan lets you invest small amounts
of money for a period of 15 years and
ensures a guaranteed income for life
so restart your life post retirement on
your own terms with icici proof
guaranteed pension plan flexi
one option this plan offers is the
single life with accelerated health
boosters
in addition to a guaranteed regular
income this option gives you additional
payouts to take care of your healthcare
needs
key benefit of the plan
in case you are diagnosed with an
inability to perform the activities of
daily living an additional payout in the
form of accelerated health boosters will
be given to you
the icici approved guaranteed pension
plan flexi also offers multiple benefits
regular income with regular savings
choice of 7 annuity options as per your
needs
unique options like accelerated health
boosters and booster payouts that
provide a periodic lump sum payout to
take care of your healthcare and
lifestyle needs
one percent additional annuity for
existing icici prudential life insurance
customers
save the date feature to receive your
income on the date of your choice
top-up facility to increase your income
by paying an additional premium
loan facility to get access to money
when you need
[Music]